======================================
README.txt - Cluster Connector NLP API
======================================

**API to connect to the Cluster Connector server from the NLP model**

Some notes on the documentation
-------------------------------

Documentation of the Python NLP Cluster API to connect the Cluster server can be found via
[this link](https://clusterdocs.azurewebsites.net/). Note that this API is still under development,
so there are a lot of upcoming changes in the implementation, but the interface as it is right now shouldn't change too
much. The interface is somewhat different to the proposed interface, but a lot is still the same.
